savebig.com 2011-12-06

# SaveBig.com - Bid to Win Amazing Deals on Electronics, Computers, Jewelry & Fashion, Home & Garden, DVDs & more - SaveBig.com

(Effective Date: 03/01/2011) 

##### Scope

SaveBig provides this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information received from Users of www.SaveBig.com. This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time, so it is important that you check back regularly for changes. By using this Site and Service as a visitor or by registering as a User, you consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy and to our Terms of Service, which should be read in conjunction with this Policy. 

##### Information Collected

When you register with the Site you will be asked for certain personally identifiable information. This means information about you that can be used to contact or identify you such as your name, username, phone number, credit card or other billing information, email address and home and business addresses. We also collect other information you provide as part of your User registration and the administration and/or personalization of your account. We may also collect information regarding your activity on the Site, such as your bidding history, any auctions you have participated in, auctions you have won or lost, prices paid, bids made and other similar information associated with your account. 

This information may be used to provide you with a better experience on the Site, to improve the quality of our Service and/or to analyze and adapt how our Site and Service are used. We may also use the information to deliver a product or products to you according to your preferences or restrictions. We also use your information to contact you with certain marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. 

If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such material from us, please [contact us](http://www.savebig.com/help/contact/) or refer to the section entitled "Changing or Deleting Information" below. 

When you visit the Site, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends via web beacons. We record information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, the webpage you were visiting before you came to our Site, pages of our Site that you visited, the amount of time spent on these pages, information you search for on our Site, access times and dates, and other related statistics. We use this information to monitor and analyze use of the Site and the Service and for the Site's technical administration, to increase our Site's functionality and user-friendliness, and to better tailor it to our visitors' needs. Some of this information is collected so that when you visit the Site again, it will recognize you and serve advertisements and other information appropriate to your interests. 

##### Use of Data

Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized experience. You agree that we may use your personal information to provide the services and customer support you request, resolve any disputes, collect fees, troubleshoot problems, prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities and enforce our Terms of Service; customize, measure and/or improve our services, content and advertising; inform you about our services, targeted marketing, service updates, and promotional offers; and compare information for accuracy or verify it with third parties. 

##### Disclosure of Data

We may disclose personal information in conformity with legal requirements, to enforce our policies, respond to claims that a particular listing or other content violates the rights of others, or protect anyone's rights, property, or safety as appropriate. Such information will be disclosed in accordance with applicable laws and regulations. We may also share your personal information with third parties assisting our business operations under contract, including but not limited to fraud investigations and debt collection, law enforcement or other governmental officials, and other business entities. 

Without limiting the above, in an effort to respect your privacy, we will not otherwise disclose your personal information to law enforcement, other government officials, or other third parties without a subpoena, court order or substantially similar legal procedure, except when we believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss or to report suspected illegal activity. 

##### Your Information

Once you have been approved as registered user with SaveBig, you will be required to choose a Username. This Username will be displayed throughout SaveBig and will therefore be visible to the public. Unless you associate your Username with your personal information, Users will not be able to personally identify you with your username or your activities on the Site. 

##### Changing / Deleting Your Information

All registered Users may review, update, correct or delete the information in their registration profile by [contacting us](http://www.savebig.com/help/contact/). If you would like us to delete you from our system, use the "Close My Account" function in My Account. We may retain an archived copy of your records as required by law or for legitimate business purposes. 

##### Use of Cookies

We use cookies to store Users' preferences and to record session information, for purposes including ensuring that users are not repeatedly offered the same advertisements and to customize newsletter, advertising, and Webpage content based on browser type and User profile information. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable data you submit while on the Site. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set - each browser is different, you may wish to review the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences - however, this may affect your ability to use certain functions or portions of the Site. Please note that we may allow third party advertisers that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Advertisers' use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not our Privacy Policy. 

We use Google Analytics, a third-party tracking service, which uses cookies to track non-personally identifiable information about our visitors to our site in the aggregate to capture usage and volume statistics. Some of our business partners (e.g. Google Analytics) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. The privacy statement covers the use of cookies by SaveBig only and does not cover the use of cookies by any third-party. 

##### Refer Friends

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. SaveBig may store this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and/or tracking the success of our referral program. Your friend may [contact us](http://www.savebig.com/help/contact/) to request that we remove this information from our database. 

##### Links and Participating Vendor Policies

The Site may contain links to participating vendor websites or third party websites to which we have no affiliation. Except as set forth herein, we do not share your personal information with those third parties or participating vendors, and are not responsible for their privacy practices. We suggest you read the privacy policies on all such third party and participating vendor websites. 

##### Testimonials

We may post customer testimonials on our site which may contain personally identifiable information. We do obtain the customers consent via email prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial. To request your testimonial to be removed please [contact us](http://www.savebig.com/help/contact/). 

##### Security

Your SaveBig account and profile and the information contained therein are password protected. You are not permitted to provide your password to anyone else. SaveBig will never ask for your password in e-mails that you receive unexpectedly or that you did not request. We assume no liability for the abuse of login data and passwords used. Although we work very hard to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private, as this may at times be outside of our control. 

##### Protection from Web Crawlers or Spam

We will not rent or sell your e-mail address to third parties, and we will prevent your e-mail address from being recorded by "web-crawlers" or "web-spiders" to the best of our ability. If you believe that your e-mail address has been recorded in this way, please let us know immediately. 

##### Children

This Site is not directed to children under 18. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with personal information without their consent, he or she should [contact us](http://www.savebig.com/help/contact/) immediately. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we will delete such information from our files. 

##### International Transfer

Your information may be transferred to and/or and maintained on computers located outside of your state, country or other governmental jurisdiction where privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your particular jurisdiction. If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to us, SaveBig transfers this personal information to the United States and processes it there. Your consent to this Privacy Policy and your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer. 

##### Questions?

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, please [contact us](http://www.savebig.com/help/contact/).
